[
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"That's the very ___ offer after losing the book.",
			"optionA":"least she could",
			"optionB":"last she could",
			"optionC":"leess she could",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"___ as I hate to do this, we'll have to cancel the party",
			"optionA":"more",
			"optionB":"much",
			"optionC":"such",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"Above ___ her priority is to finish her degree course.",
			"optionA":"any",
			"optionB":"every",
			"optionC":"all",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"Paul doesn't have many friends, just a select ___.",
			"optionA":"few",
			"optionB":"little",
			"optionC":"half",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"___ way, they're going to close the deal.",
			"optionA":"Both",
			"optionB":"Either",
			"optionC":"Each",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"Polo is a sport that is associated with ___ rich and powerful.",
			"optionA":"some",
			"optionB":"a",
			"optionC":"the",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"There was ___ a time when I had to help him.",
			"optionA":"many",
			"optionB":"more than",
			"optionC":"much",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"I've had ___ of his complaints.",
			"optionA":"every",
			"optionB":"enough",
			"optionC":"other",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"We had many candidates, but ___ was good for the position.",
			"optionA":"much of them",
			"optionB":"neither of them",
			"optionC":"none of them",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"That country has two official languages, but ___ is English.",
			"optionA":"neither of them",
			"optionB":"none of them",
			"optionC":"both of them",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"They cost 2 dollars ___.",
			"optionA":"either",
			"optionB":"each",
			"optionC":"every",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"___ argument could move ___ man from this decision.",
			"optionA":"Each / all",
			"optionB":"No / neither",
			"optionC":"No / either ",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"___ Peter ___ Michael often come here but ___ of them help us.",
			"optionA":"Both / and / neither ",
			"optionB":"Both / and / either",
			"optionC":"Neither / nor / both",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"He gave ___ of us advice about our present goals.",
			"optionA":"every",
			"optionB":"each",
			"optionC":"much",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"___ players played well; In fact they ___ played quite badly.",
			"optionA":"neither of / both",
			"optionB":"neither of the / all",
			"optionC":"none of the / all",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"There were ___ on the beach, so we weren't completely alone.",
			"optionA":"a few",
			"optionB":"fewer",
			"optionC":"fewest",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"___ them were tired, because ___ them had slept well.",
			"optionA":"None of / either of",
			"optionB":"Both of / neither of",
			"optionC":"Either of / none of",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"We should have a check up with the dentist ___ six months.",
			"optionA":"all",
			"optionB":"each",
			"optionC":"every",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	}
]